Inventory of the Papers of Judge John W. Bissell, 1983-2005
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Papers, 1987 (Box 9-13)
  - Cardoso v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1987 May 18 (Box 9)
    Letter-Opinion; Errata Order; Order
  - Chambers v. Pub. Serv. Elec. & Gas Co. 1987 July 08 (Box 9)
  - Ciaravino v. Dir. 1987 October 01 (Box 9)
    Disaster relief and insurance
    Natural disasters
    Floods and storm protection
  - Cole v. Pathmark of Fairlawn 1987 October 30 (Box 9)
  - Computran Sys. Corp. v. Inductotherm Indus. 1987 October 08 (Box 9)
  - Conn. Gen. Life Ins. Co. v. E. Dental Ctr. of Ewing 1987 October 09 (Box 9)
    General health and health care finance matters
  - Cooper v. Tard 1987 October 09 (Box 9)
  - Cox v. Metro. Life Ins. Co. 1987 June 24 (Box 9)
  - Davis v. Sec'y of Health and Human Serv. 1987 November 09 (Box 9)
  - Davis v. Rafferty 1987 September 16 (Box 9)
  - Deeks v. Lake 1987 September 21 (Box 9)
    Deeks v. Lake, No. 85-2947, 1987 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 14873 (D. N.J. Apr. 30, 1987); No. 85-2947, 1987 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 14875 (D. N.J. Sept. 21, 1987).
  - Dunn v. New Jersey Transit Corp. 1987 November 13 (Box 10)
    Opinion; Order; Corrected pages marked "Corrections sent to West" (Published at 681 F.Supp. 246 (D.N.J.,1987))
  - Durrof v. Pike County Dev. Ctr. 1987 February 17 (Box 10)
  - Dutka v. Bello 1987 May 29 (Box 10)
    Letter-Opinion; Order Granting Judgment | Letter-Opinion; Order (1986 June 22) | Letter-Opinion; Order for Dismissal (1986 April 17)
  - Euro Imp. v. Roth 1987 December 14 (Box 10)
  - Falter v. Veterans Admin. 1987 March 11 (Box 10)
    Letter from A.U.S.A. Anne C. Singer; Letter from William F. Culleton, Jr.
  - Farlow v. Fed. Bureau of Investigation 1987 August 21 (Box 10)
  - Federowitz v. Goldman 1987 March 10 (Box 10)
  - Fidelity Union Bank v. United States 1987 January 05 (Box 10)
    Opinion; Order | Transcript of Proceedings (1987 October 02)
  - Figueroa v. Rafferty 1987 June 17 (Box 10)
  - Football Generals, Inc. v. J. W. Duncan, Inc. 1987 November 18 (Box 10)
    Games and hobbies
    Professional sports
  - Frankel v. Shearson Lehman Bros. 1987 October 30 (Box 10)
    Frankel v. Shearson Lehman Bros., No. 86-2520, 1987 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16099 (D. N.J. Oct. 30, 1987).
  - Freund v. Bowen 1987 May 01 (Box 10)
  - Garolis v. Tr. of the Trucking Employees of N. Jersey Welfare Fund 1987 June 30 (Box 10)
  - General Electric Co. v. Heis 1987 December 07 (Box 10)
    Opinion; Order for Preliminary Injunction
  - Gleis v. Norman 1987 September 10 (Box 10)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1987 September 21)
  - Grace v. City of Newark 1987 May 13 (Box 10)
  - Granados v. U.S. Immigration 1987 December 28 (Box 10)
    Foreign labor
    Immigration status and procedures
    Refugees, asylum, displaced persons
    Visas and passports
  - Gross v. Xerox Corp. 1987 March 06 (Box 10)
  - Gruhin v. Insall 1987 June 25 (Box 10)
  - Haight v. Grund 1987 November 24 (Box 10)
  - Hardy v. Maucelli & Parkwood Gardens Assoc. 1987 October 26 (Box 10)
    Housing supply and affordability
    Low- and moderate-income housing
  - Helbig v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. 1987 January 29 (Box 10)
  - Henry v. Beyer 1987 December 28 (Box 10)
  - Horowitz Fin. Corp. v. Wolf Creek Vill., Inc. 1987 May 05 (Box 10)
  - Huiswoud v. Cuozzo 1987 June 24 (Box 10)
  - Int'l Paint Co. v. Myers Eng'g, Inc. 1987 August 14 (Box 10)
    Product development and innovation
  - Jackson v. United States 1987 July 27 (Box 10)
    Employment taxes
  - Jodeco v. Hann 1987 December 04 (Box 11)
    Land transfers
    Advisory bodies
    Government buildings, facilities, and property
    Appropriations
  - Jones v. City of Paterson 1987 December 14 (Box 11)
  - Karlen v. Tribune Cable Commc'n 1987 May 26 (Box 11)
  - Karolis v. Beyers 1987 November 30 (Box 11)
  - Kievit v. Rokeach 1987 October 29 (Box 11)
    Opinion; Order; Order; Order
    Commodities markets
    Kievit v. Rokeach, No. 91-2907, 1987 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16131 (D. N.J. Oct. 29, 1987).
  - Kilbarr Corp. v. Amsterdam-Rotterdam Bank 1987 March 10 (Box 11)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1987 November 16)
  - La Pollo v. Gen. Elec. Co. 1987 July 15 (Box 11)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.C. Senior Judge Mitchell H. Cohen); Order
  - Lair v. Fauver 1987 May 29 (Box 11)
  - Lantz v. Loral Packaging 1987 February 09 (Box 11)
  - Lynch v. Gore 1987 October 15 (Box 11)
  - MacKenzie v. City of Newark 1987 September 30 (Box 11)
  - Mallon v. Prudential Prop. & Cas. Ins. Co. 1987 May 26 (Box 11)
  - McCarty v. Am. Cyanamid Co. 1987 December 23 (Box 11)
  - McCutchen v. G.H. Realty Co. 1987 April 24 (Box 11)
    Poverty and welfare assistance
  - McIsaac v. Kanematsu-Gosho, Inc. 1987 March 13 (Box 11)
    Opinion; Judgment and Order
  - McMahan v. Bowen 1987 June 29 (Box 11)
  - McManus v. Hous. Auth. of Englewood 1987 April 10 (Box 11)
  - Meadows v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1987 June 24 (Box 11)
    Memorandum Opinion and Order
  - Mele v. Bowen 1987 August 14 (Box 11)
  - Metall-Chemie Handelgesell-Schaft m.b.H. & Co. v. Seacor 1987 March 17 (Box 11)
  - Miller v. Anscher 1987 June 25 (Box 11)
  - Miller v. U.S. Capital Corp. 1987 December 01 (Box 11)
    South Carolina
  - Miraglia v. D'Ilio 1987 August 13 (Box 11)
  - Misiewicz v. Bowen 1987 November 06 (Box 11)
  - Monon Corp. v. Centre Serv. 1987 December 23 (Box 11)
  - Mt. Everest Ski Shops v. Ski Barn, Inc. 1987 April 03 (Box 11)
    Vermont
  - Najafi v. Rosen 1987 April 27 (Box 11)
    Military medicine
  - Napier v. Philips, Appel & Walden 1987 July 06 (Box 11)
  - N.J. Dep't of Envtl. Prot. v. Gloucester Envtl. Serv. 1987 August 20 (Box 11)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Stanley S. Brotman); Order
  - Newark Morning Ledger Co. v. Newspaper & Mail Deliverers Union 1987 February 13 (Box 11)
  - Olitsky v. Rafferty 1987 April 30 (Box 11)
  - Organon v. Int'l Union of Elec. Workers 1987 September 28 (Box 12)
  - Orr v. Sterling Limousine Corp. 1987 December 18 (Box 12)
  - Patnode v. Horowitz 1987 September 21 (Box 12)
  - Pecone v. United States 1987 February 18 (Box 12)
    Radioactive wastes and releases
    Government corporations and government-sponsored enterprises
  - In re Period Design Homes 1987 April 30 (Box 12)
  - Perkins v. Fauver 1987 January 27 (Box 12)
  - Perretti v. Serraino 1987 June 10 (Box 12)
  - Policemen's Benevolent Ass'n of N.J. v. Twp. of Washington 1987 October 08 (Box 12)
    Opinion with Judgment and Order (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Joseph H. Rodriguez)
    Law enforcement administration and funding
  - Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. v. U.S. Gypsum, Inc. 1987 March 28 (Box 12)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Harold A. Ackerman)
  - Quantum Prod. Serv. v. Pub. Serv. Gas & Electric Co. 1987 May 28 (Box 12)
  - Rabil-Alamin v. Passaic County Tech. & Vocational High Sch. 1987 September 29 (Box 12)
  - Ragland v. Tard 198706110 (Box 12)
  - Randolph v. Brown 1987 March 03 (Box 12)
  - Redding v. Dietz 1987 June 10 (Box 12)
  - Schaefer v. Bateman Eichler Hill Richards, Inc. 1987 February 09 (Box 12)
  - Sebastian Int'l v. Consumer Contacts 1987 June 30 (Box 12)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Maryanne Trump Barry); Order
  - Sellers v. Johnson 1987 October 14 (Box 12)
  - Shields v. Murphy 1987 August 04 (Box 12)
  - Smith v. Englehardt 1987 August 14 (Box 12)
  - Smith v. U.S. Sav. & Loan Ass'n 1987 October 16 (Box 12)
  - State v. Thomas 1987 October 13 (Box 12)
  - Taylor v. State 1987 April 16 (Box 12)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1987 August 17)
  - Teltser v. Czin 1987 August 17 (Box 12)
  - Temco Home Health Care Prod. v. Everest & Jennings 1987 November 12 (Box 12)
  - Thomas v. Meese 1987 May 27 (Box 12)
    Opinion; Order; Dismissal Order
  - Thomas v. State 1987 February 26 (Box 12)
  - Thornbury v. Am. Vermiculite Corp. 1987 March 10 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Cannon 1987 June 12 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Farber 1987 October 02 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Horace Mann Ins. Co. 1987 June 29 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Nelson No Date (Box 12)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Maryanne Trump Barry)
  - United States v. Perticone 1987 January 05 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Prieto 1987 September 29 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Russo 1987 May 26 (Box 12)
  - United States v. Salconi 1987 February 11 (Box 13)
  - United States v. Stine 1987 February 03 (Box 13)
  - United States v. Surretsky 1987 August 05 (Box 13)
  - Walker v. Goodyear Serv. Store 1987 March 26 (Box 13)
  - Washington v. Conrail 1987 March 20 (Box 13)
  - Weatherspoon v. Curtiss-Wright Flight Sys. 1987 July 21 (Box 13)
  - Zamboni v. Stamler 1987 June 10 (Box 13)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1987 November 30)
- Papers, 1988 (Box 13-17)
  All papers dated 1988.
  - Abd-Allah v. Neubert 1988 November 29 (Box 13)
  - Aetna Cas. & Surety Co. v. Moran 1988 March 03 (Box 13)
  - Agosto v. Hous. Auth. of Hoboken 1988 May 25 (Box 13)
    Public housing
  - Ali v. City of Linden 1988 October 24 (Box 13)
  - Anastasio v. Schering Corp. 1988 June 06 (Box 13)
    Opinion; Exhibit A
  - Anthony Petroleum, Inc. v. Baii Banking Corp. 1988 June 21 (Box 13)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1988 October 27)
  - Aquatherm Prod. Corp. v. James Wholesale Drug Co. 1988 January 15 (Box 13)
  - Banfield v. Middlesex County Adult Corr. Ctr. 1988 September 13 (Box 13)
  - Berkner v. Epstein 1988 January 22 (Box 13)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Letter-Opinion; Order (1988 January 29) | Letter-Opinion; Order (1988 March 24)
  - Berson v. Alexander & Alexander, Inc. 1988 May 09 (Box 13)
  - Blum v. Wico Chem. Corp. 1988 December 27 (Box 13)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. H. Lee Sarokin)
  - Brito v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 13)
    Opinion and Order
  - Broski v. Pennsylvania 1988 January 15 (Box 13)
  - Brown v. Grabowski 1988 January 06 (Box 13)
  - Brown v. Neubert 1988 August 29 (Box 13)
  - Bryant v. Bowen 1988 March 03 (Box 13)
    Bryant v. Bowen, 683 F. Supp. 95 (D. N.J. 1988).
  - Chemisphere Tech. Corp. v. Metalx 1988 July 28 (Box 13)
  - China Ocean Shipping Co. v. Maher Terminals 1988 January 20 (Box 13)
  - Christopher v. Gabriel 1988 November 30 (Box 13)
  - Clayton v. Beyer 1988 May 25 (Box 13)
  - Clemons v. Fauver 1988 May 18 (Box 13)
  - Crest Audio v. Dunlop Mfg. 1988 July 20 (Box 13)
  - Crowell v. Menchin 1988 July 27 (Box 13)
  - Davis v. Prudential Ins. Co. of Am. 1988 July 21 (Box 13)
  - Deeks v. Lake 1988 August 01 (Box 13)
    Deeks v. Lake, No. 85-2947, 1988 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16686 (D. N.J. May 25, 1988).
  - Delgado v. Twp. of West New York 1988 June 15 (Box 13)
  - Demby v. N.J. Dep't of Corr. 1988 June 20 (Box 14)
  - Des Moines '81 Assoc. v. F.W. Woolworth & Co. 1988 July 21 (Box 14)
    Iowa
  - Duffy v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 14)
  - Dynatron/Bondo Corp. v. Clausen Co. 1988 September 22 (Box 14)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1988 November 30)
  - In re Elsinore Shore Assoc. 1988 February 03 (Box 14)
  - Enprotech Corp. v. Renda 1988 February 12 (Box 14)
    Opinion; Order; Exhibits A, B | Opinion; Order (1988 November 04) | Opinion; Order (1988 November 16)
    Employement discrimination and employee rights
  - Essex Chem. Corp. v. Gruit-Heberlein AG 1988 June 24 (Box 14)
    Essex Chem. Corp. v. Gruit-Heberlein AG, No. 88-2478, 1988 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 19515 (D. N.J. June 24, 1988).; No. 88-2478, 1988 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 16708 (D. N.J. June 24, 1988).
  - Federowicz v. Goldman 1988 October 11 (Box 14)
  - Filter Equip. Co. v. Membrana Corp. 1988 January 22 (Box 14)
  - Food Fresh, Inc. v. Stay Fresh, Ltd. 1988 May 31 (Box 14)
  - Football Generals, Inc. v. J.W. Duncan, Inc. 1988 October 14 (Box 14)
  - Franchise Stores Realty Corp. v. Ross 1988 January 28 (Box 14)
  - Frankel v. Shearson Lehman Bros., Inc. 1988 December 08 (Box 14)
  - Gadson v. Baer 1988 August 09 (Box 14)
  - Geeter v. Marsh 1988 January 06 (Box 14)
  - Gen. Biscuit Brands v. R.K.D. Oil Co. 1988 May 23 (Box 14)
  - Gen. Elec. Co. v. Heis 1988 September 14 (Box 14)
    Opinion; Final Judgment
  - Gomez v. Iberia Airlines of Spain 1988 March 17 (Box 14)
    Travel and tourism
    International law and treaties
    Tariffs
  - Granados v. U.S. Immigration 1988 November 30 (Box 14)
    Philippines
  - Green v. Bowen 1988 April 11 (Box 14)
  - Groel v. L.F. Rothschild & Co. 1988 June 28 (Box 14)
  - Gulf & W. Mfg. Co. v. United Steelworkers of Am. 1988 February 09 (Box 14)
    Gulf & W. Mfg. Co. v. United Steelworkers of Am., 694 F. Supp. 38 (D. N.J. 1988).
  - Gussin Gen. P'ship v. Sabarese 1988 December 08 (Box 14)
    Opinion; Affidavit of Alfred C. Constants III; Order
  - Guzman v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 14)
  - Harden v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 14)
  - Hardy v. Maucelli 1988 September 13 (Box 14)
  - Harris v. Commc'n Techniques, Inc. 1988 December 30 (Box 14)
  - Heaton v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 14)
  - Hellring Lindeman Goldstein Siegal Stern & Greenberg v. Skulsky 1988 February 29 (Box 14)
  - Holloway v. U.S. Postal Serv. 1988 January 20 (Box 14)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Letter-Opinion; Order (1988 March 02)
  - Horowitz Fin. Corp. v. Ingersoll & Bloch Chartered 1988 September 22 (Box 14)
  - Hudak v. Unisonic Prod. Corp. 1988 April 07 (Box 15)
    Transcript of Proceedings; Judgment
  - Improta v. Weehawken Bd. of Ed. 1988 October 18 (Box 15)
  - Ins. Co. of N. Am. v. Hop-On Int'l Corp. 1988 September 30 (Box 15)
  - Int'l Ladies' Garment Workers Union, Local 220 v. Solomon 1988 September 23 (Box 15)
  - Int'l Union v. Curtiss-Wright Corp. 1988 October 25 (Box 15)
  - J. Gerber & Co. v. First Fidelity Bank 1988 March 21 (Box 15)
  - J.I. Hass Co. v. Gilbane Bldg. Co. 1988 May 25 (Box 15)
  - Jersey Cent. Power & Light Co. v. Int'l Union of Operating Eng'r 1988 July 29 (Box 15)
    Opinion; Exhibit A; Order
  - Kaufman v. Hoffman La-Roche, Inc. 1988 September 13 (Box 15)
  - Key v. Tisch 1988 May 11 (Box 15)
  - Kilbarr Corp. v. Business Sys., Inc. 1988 February 10 (Box 15)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1988 May 31) | Opinion; Order (1988 June 01)
    Foreign and international corporations
  - Kirker Chem. Co. v. Sanfilippo 1988 July 27 (Box 15)
  - Koproski v. Cottle 1988 December 20 (Box 15)
  - Lacewell v. U.S. Dep't of Hous. & Urban Dev. 1988 October 19 (Box 15)
  - Lee v. Carey Canada, Inc. 1988 May 25 (Box 15)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1988 December 01)
  - Leige v. Am. Hoist & Derrick Co. 1988 November 29 (Box 15)
  - Lynch v. Consolidated R.R. Corp. 1988 September 22 (Box 15)
    Opinion; Order Granting Summary Judgment in Favor of Defendant
  - Lyons Capital Res. v. Rome Diagnostic Assoc. 1988 September 14 (Box 15)
    Letter-Opinion; Order | Transcript of Proceedings (1988 March 09); Order
  - Maher v. Siemens Medical Sys. 1988 February 08 (Box 15)
  - Mallon v. Prudential Prop. & Cas. Ins. Co. 1988 May 10 (Box 15)
    Mallon v. Prudential Prop. & Cas. Ins. Co., 688 F. Supp. 997 (D. N.J. 1988).
  - Manfra v. Hertz Corp. 1988 March 03 (Box 15)
  - Marotta Scientific Controls v. RLI Ins. Co. 1988 February 25 (Box 15)
    Opinion; Order for Dismissal | Letter-Opinion; Order (1988 March 16)
  - Martinez v. United States 1988 September 07 (Box 15)
  - McKenna v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 15)
  - McMillan v. Lincoln Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n 1988 February 09 (Box 15)
    McMillan v. Lincoln Fed. Sav. & Loan Ass'n, 678 F. Supp. 89 (D. N.J. 1988).
  - McSwain v. Beyer 1988 March 11 (Box 15)
  - Meyer v. Int'l Playtex 1988 December 01 (Box 15)
    Meyer v. Int'l Playtex, 724 F. Supp. 288 (D. N.J. 1988).
  - Monon Corp. v. Ctr. Serv. 1988 January 11 (Box 15)
    Transcript of Proceedings | Opinion; Order (1988 September 14)
  - Narvaez v. Rodriguez 1988 June 15 (Box 15)
    Alternative treatments
  - Nebus v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 15)
  - Netelkos v. Star Ledger 1988 May 20 (Box 15)
  - Netelkos v. Weinberg 1988 May 20 (Box 16)
  - O'Brien v. Borough of Woodbury Heights 1988 February 11 (Box 16)
  - Peaceman v. S.B. Thomas, Inc. 1988 January 06 (Box 16)
  - Poole v. Stephens 1988 May 16 (Box 16)
    Poole v. Stephens, 688 F. Supp. 149 (D. N.J. 1988).
  - Porter v. ITT Corp. 1988 April 04 (Box 16)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (undated) │ Opinion; Order
  - Provident Sav. Bank v. Aspen Impressions, Inc. 1988 September 28 (Box 16)
  - Reliance Sav. & Loan Ass'n v. CNA 1988 May 23 (Box 16)
    Transcript of Proceedings | Opinion; Order (1988 July 28)
  - RFAC Int'l v. IBM 1988 July 01 (Box 16)
    Amended Opinion
  - Rosen v. Union of Am. Hebrew Congregation 1988 November 30 (Box 16)
  - Roxas v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 16)
  - RPM Dev. Corp. v. City of Orange Twp. 1988 December 08 (Box 16)
  - Seamon v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 16)
  - Sec. Investor Protection Corp. v. Christian-Paine & Co. 1988 September 23 (Box 16)
    Government trust funds
  - Sellers v. Marcik 1988 March 29 (Box 16)
  - Skandia Ins. Co. v. McDonnell Douglas Helicopters 1988 December 21 (Box 16)
    Opinion; Order Dismissing Complaint against Defendant
  - Spiegel v. State 1988 September 14 (Box 16)
  - Stigliano v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 16)
  - Stocker v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 16)
  - Student Pub. Interest Research Group of N.J. v. Am. Cyanamid Co. 1988 July 21 (Box 16)
    Marine pollution
    Student Pub. Interest Research Group of N.J. v. Am. Cyanamid Co., No. 83-2068, 1988 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 17241 (D. N.J. July 21, 1988).
  - Sussex Drug Prod. Co. v. Kanasco 1988 March 16 (Box 16)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1988 June 15)
    Veterinary medicine and animal diseases
  - Tillman v. State 1988 March 03 (Box 16)
  - U.S. Golf Ass'n v. U.S. Amateur Golf Ass'n 1988 August 05 (Box 16)
    Opinion and Order (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Nicholas H. Politan)
  - United States v. Algon Chem., Inc. 1988 April 12 (Box 16)
    Food supply, safety, and labeling
    Trade restrictions
  - United States v. Ten Slot Machines 1988 January 27 (Box 16)
  - United States v. Anthony Dell'Aquila Enter. 1988 August 11 (Box 16)
    United States v. Anthony Dell'Aquila Enter., No. 88-3232, 1988 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 17097 (D. N.J. Aug. 5, 1988).
  - United States v. Basulto 1988 February 09 (Box 16)
  - United States v. Freeman 1988 June 06 (Box 16)
    Opinion; Order Granting Partial Summary Judgment and Final Judgment | Opinion; Order; Order (1988 December 02)
  - United States v. Gambino 1988 March 10 (Box 16)
  - United States v. Kraselnick 1988 December 22 (Box 16)
  - United States v. Vargas 1988 November 01 (Box 16)
  - United States v. Villard 1988 February 11 (Box 16)
    Opinion (Opinion of U.S.D.J. Joseph H. Rodriguez)
  - United States v. Wilson 1988 February 18 (Box 16)
  - United States v. Zapata 1988 March 02 (Box 16)
  - Vetere v. United States 1988 October 24 (Box 17)
  - Viggiani v. U.S. Postal Office 1988 December 08 (Box 17)
    Federally chartered organizations
  - Waigand v. Equal Employment Opportunity Program 1988 September 14 (Box 17)
  - Walizer v. Bowen 1988 February 19 (Box 17)
  - Washington v. Tisch 1988 April 05 (Box 17)
  - Welsh v. Truck Drivers & Chauffeurs Union, Local 478 1988 July 21 (Box 17)
  - West v. Conrail 1988 March 29 (Box 17)
  - Williamson v. N.J. Transit Rail Operations 1988 April 06 (Box 17)
- Papers, 1989 (Box 17-21)
  All papers dated 1989.
  - A M Int'l v. Hartz Mountain Indus. 1989 October 06 (Box 17)
  - Abate v. Monroe Sys. for Bus. 1989 May 08 (Box 17)
    Opinion; Order; Amended Order
  - Allen v. City of Jersey City 1989 December 04 (Box 17)
    Education programs funding
  - Am. Body & Equip. v. Meyer Prod. 1989 July 12 (Box 17)
  - Am. Cyanamid Co. v. S.C. Johnson & Sons 1989 August 30 (Box 17)
    Am. Cyanamid Co. v. S.C. Johnson & Sons, 729 F. Supp. 1018 (D. N.J. 1989).
  - Anello v. Merck & Co. 1989 May 10 (Box 17)
  - Aviles v. Am. Newark Assoc. 1989 April 20 (Box 17)
  - Bello v. Middlesex County Adult Corr. Ctr. 1989 April 04 (Box 17)
    Opinion; Order and Order to Show Cause | Opinion; Order (1989 June 01)
  - Bellotti v. United States 1989 February 01 (Box 17)
  - Berkner v. Epstein 1989 February 02 (Box 17)
    Animal and plant health
  - Book v. Postmaster 1989 October 02 (Box 17)
  - In re Brinke Transp. Corp. 1989 July 18 (Box 17)
    In re Brinke Transp. Corp., No. 89-1778, 1989 U.S. Dist. LEXIS 17577 (D. N.J. July 18, 1989).
  - Brown v. Grabowski 1989 May 25 (Box 17)
  - Bryant v. Motivated Guard Serv. 1989 January 25 (Box 17)
  - Chan v. Philippine Airlines 1989 September 19 (Box 17)
  - Ciano v. American-Darling Valve 1989 November 30 (Box 17)
  - Conoco v. Tank Barge Interstate 36 1989 February 02 (Box 17)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1989 May 12)
  - Consol. Rail Corp. v. City of Bayonne 1989 October 12 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion (19891109
    Transportation safety and security
    Federal preemption
    Consol. Rail Corp. v. City of Bayonne, 724 F. Supp. 320 (D. N.J. 1989).
  - Control Air v. Am. Trans-Freight 1989 December 01 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order; Order Setting Aside Default
  - CPC Int'l v. Int'l Ins. Co. 1989 March 27 (Box 18)
  - Davis v. Milford Jai Alai 1989 October 10 (Box 18)
  - Davis v. Waterfront & Airport Comm'n 1989 May 10 (Box 18)
  - Del. Valley Transplant Program v. Coye 1989 October 16 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order (Opinion and Order of U.S.D.J Stanley S. Brotman)
    Organ and tissue donation and transplantation
  - Dole v. Int'l Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers Local 427 1989 April 11 (Box 18)
  - Dynatron/Bondo Corp. v. Clausen Co. 1989 January 25 (Box 18)
  - Enprotech Corp. v. Renda v. C. Itoh & Co. 1989 February 21 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order
  - Entran Devices v. Interocean Sys. 1989 June 16 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Exhibits 21, 22; Judgment
  - F. von Langsdorf Licensing v. Grinnell Concrete Paving-Stones, Inc. 1989 June 19 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1989 September 01)
  - Farash v. Robert Tabakow Co. 1989 January 26 (Box 18)
  - Fed. Nat'l Mortgage Ass'n v. Casey 1989 August 24 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order (Order 19890825)
  - Florabelle Flowers v. Bos 1989 July 05 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order | Opinion; Order (1989 November 13)
  - Football Generals v. Duncan 1989 May 09 (Box 18)
  - Forest Park Apartments v. Sylvan Coin Laundry 1989 November 20 (Box 18)
  - Figatner v. Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner, & Smith 1989 August 16 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Order Granting Summary Judgment
  - Firetek Corp. v. Nat'l Guardian Sec. Serv. Corp. 1989 June 01 (Box 18)
    Opinion | Opinion (1989 September 18)
  - First Fidelity Bank v. Parness 1989 December 12 (Box 18)
  - Frank Music Corp. v. Thirty Harding Ave. 1989 May 24 (Box 18)
    Opinion; Default Judgment
    Sound recording
  - Golden City Bank v. Rutherford Commercial Corp. 1989 October 06 (Box 18)
  - Gov't of the Virgin Islands v. Commissiong 1989 February 16 (Box 18)
    U.S. territories and protectorates
  - Gumbs v. Cielo 1989 September 01 (Box 18)
    Opinion | Affidavit (1989 August 03) | Certification Supporting Application for Entry of Default Judgment by Clerk (1989 April 17) | Request to Enter Default (1989 March 03) | Summons & Complaint (copy) (1987 October 16) | Exhibits B, C
  - Hardwick v. Cuomo 1989 April 12 (Box 19)
    Tax reform and tax simplification
    State and local taxation
    Tax treatment of families
    Income tax credits
  - Hargreaves v. Passaic Metal Prod. 1989 February 03 (Box 19)
  - Harris v. Eisenberg, Honig & Fogler 1989 July 13 (Box 19)
  - Harris v. Schiedemantel 1989 May 02 (Box 19)
  - Heller v. Carter 1989 December 15 (Box 19)
  - Howard Johnson Franchise Sys. v. Musikantow 1989 October 06 (Box 19)
  - Int'l Union v. Curtiss-Wright Corp. 1989 February 22 (Box 19)